(Howard:)Hey, Ma.
(Howard:)You know, we could see each other
if you turn on the computer.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)I'm not going near that fakakta thing.
I'll catch a computer virus!
(Howard:)You can't catch a computer virus.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Oh, so now you're an astronaut
and a doctor?
(Howard:)What do you want, Ma?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Your wife says you have
something important to tell me.
Okay, here it is:
(Howard:)Bernadette and I
are starting a life together.
(Sheldon:)- And...
- Oh, God.
You are gonna leave me!
(Sheldon:)- Ma...
- It's okay.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Your father left me, you left me.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)I guess I'm just the kind of person
people like to leave.
(Howard:)It's not definite. I'll talk to Bernadette.